<books>
    <book ID="IlluminatiSwag_Monsters_Prophet" Title="IlluminatiSwag_Monsters_Prophet">
        <page>I know what you have done.</page>
        <page>The stars wander darkling in the eternal space, rayless and pathless.</page>
        <page>The self is a category error.</page>
        <page>Outside of time I found myself in a place of light.</page>
        <page>For a millennium now I've watched the river of Time turn the gears of Qud.</page>
        <page>The void yawns under you. Something terrible is born.</page>
        <page>Your own hand will vaporize your purpose.</page>
        <page>New creatures struggle to be born.</page>
        <page>The Gyre has widened.</page>
        <page>The Gyre widens.</page>
        <page>The Gyre will widen.</page>
        <page>The time-arcs of the Nephilim begin to intersect this thread.</page>
        <page>That which is finite has always already ended.</page>
        <page>I will be freed from my prison.</page>
        <page>The Elder will be freed from its prison.</page>
        <page>You will be freed from your prison.</page>
        <page>We will be freed from our prison.</page>
        <page>The sightless eye is upon you always.</page>
        <page>There is life even in the uttermost voids.</page>
        <page>With every action, a thousand worlds are severed from this thread.</page>
        <page>You are already dead.</page>
        <page>You died a million years ago.</page>
        <page>The Elder has waited.</page>
        <page>The Elder waits.</page>
        <page>The Elder will wait.</page>
        <page>I am a worm in the loam of a cosmic wood, perched on a cosmic gulf, swathed in the god-manifold.</page>
        <page>You are a little sapfly resting in the crook of a swarmshade tree.</page>
        <page>Sight guides us no more than salt does.</page>
        <page>The aether speaks. Can you hear it?</page>
        <page>The Elder hears without listening, talks without speaking, sees without sight.</page>
        <page>Lemma: The category of presheaves on a k-dimensional subspace of the psychic aether is k-isomorphic to the oneirotopos of that space.</page>
        <page>Theorem: The Kleisli dual of Tl&#148;n-embedded entheological concurrency is a multithelitic comaenad on the Domain of Amaranth.</page>
        <page>The moon wanes.</page>
        <page>A kingdom wanes and sets.</page>
    </book>
</books>